midco.com 2019-05-25

# Privacy Statement

### Online Privacy Policy

_Updated January 2016_

This Online Privacy Policy applies to your use of websites and interactive services that are owned, operated or provided by Midcontinent Communications® or our affiliates (collectively, “Midco®,” “we” or “us”) and that display an authorized link to this policy (collectively, the “Services”). As of April 2014, these websites include Midco.com, [Midco.com/Business](https://www.midco.com/business "Midco Business"), [Midco.net](http://www.midco.net/ "Midco Net") and [MidcoSN.com](http://www.midcosn.com/ "Midco Sports Network"). Since 1931, Midco has been committed to providing our customers with outstanding quality, customer service, and value. Our Online Privacy Policy continues our commitment to serve you and to protect your privacy online. This Online Privacy Policy applies only to the information we and others may collect online through the Services. Visit Midco.com/Legal to see the separate privacy policies that apply to our cable television, Internet, and telephone customers.

By using any of our Services, you agree that this Online Privacy Policy and the Visitor Agreement (below) govern your use of our Services and any dispute over privacy. In addition, by using any of our Services, you authorize us to collect and disclose information about you and your use of the Services to the extent set forth herein and in the Visitor Agreement. If you object to these disclosures, do not continue to use the Services. Your use of the Services constitutes your authorization for the collection and disclosure of this information. Please take a few minutes to read this Online Privacy Policy and Visitor Agreement before using or registering to access our Services.

Please read this Online Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our privacy practices regarding:

  * Children under 13
  * Information collected through our Services
  * How we use the information we collect
  * How we disclose information
  * Sites to which we link
  * How to correct or update your information
  * Newsletters and promotions
  * Security
  * Retention and storage of information
  * Changes to our Online Privacy Policy

If you have questions about this Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at [webmaster@midco.net](mailto:webmaster@midco.net).

**Children Under 13:**

Midco cares about protecting the privacy of children. We will not knowingly allow anyone under the age of 13 to provide us any personally identifying information online. Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. We encourage you to become involved in your children’s online experience, and to share your interest in our Services with them. If you are under 13, please do not register for access to any of our Services or provide us with any personally identifying information (such as your name, your email address or your phone number).

**Information Collected Through Our Services:**

The information we gather through our Services falls into two categories: (1) information you voluntarily supply to us when you register, initiate transactions, or communicate with us through the Services, and (2) tracking information collected as you navigate through our Services. Third-party providers and advertisers featured on, or linked to from, our Services may also gather information through processes that we do not control and are subject to their own separate privacy policies, which may differ from ours.

**Registration and Other Personally Identifying Information.** We will ask you to register to use certain features of our Services. When you register, we collect personally identifying information about you, including your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, user name and password, reminder questions and answers, and communications preferences, such as which newsletters you would like to receive. We may also ask for some additional information, such as age, gender, hobbies, interests etc., but you are free to register without providing this information if you prefer. When you register for one of our websites, the information you provide will be added to a centralized Midco database so that you will simultaneously be registered for our other sites as well. In addition, when you use various aspects of our Services, we may ask you for personally identifying information, including when you: place an order for products, complete a survey, enter a contest or other promotion, or report a problem with one of our Services. We and our authorized third-party service providers use this information to process your orders, to tailor our Services to your interests and to make them more useful to you, and to help improve our Services generally. Payment and identity verification information such as credit card numbers, driver’s license numbers, social security numbers, or other national identification information, is used only for completing a particular transaction or fulfilling a service, or as otherwise required by law. We also collect contact information for other individuals when you use the sharing tools available within some of our Services to forward content or offers to your friends and associates. We use this information only to facilitate the communications that you request.

**Contests and Other Promotions.** We or our marketing or advertising partners may sometimes offer contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions. If you choose to participate in one of these promotions, you will have to provide some information about yourself (such as your name, address, and email address). If you are selected as a winner, you may also be required to provide information from your driver’s license or other government-issued identification to verify your identity or provide your Social Security Number to comply with applicable tax reporting requirements. We may share your entry information with other sponsors of the contest or other promotional partners, or they may collect it directly, but if we collect it we always will identify the other parties involved (for example, in the contest rules) and provide notice that your entry information may be disclosed to these parties. We do not control these third parties’ privacy practices, and this Online Privacy Policy does not apply to their collection and use of your information. We urge you to review their privacy policies and learn how they will use your information before participating. If you do not want us, our co-sponsors, or partners to collect the information requested in connection with a promotion, or to share that information, please do not participate in the promotion.

**Information Collected Automatically When You Use Our Services.** Midco or third-party contractors acting on our behalf may collect certain information automatically when you use our Services, including:

  * Your browser type, language, plug-ins, Internet domain,and operating system
  * Your Internet Protocol (IP) address (a numerical address assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data, such as the web pages you want to view, can be transmitted to your computer) that can sometimes be used to derive your general geographic area
  * Sites you visited before and after visiting a Midco website
  * Web pages and advertisements you view and links you click on while navigating within our Services
  * Unique identifiers, including mobile device identification numbers, that can identify the physical location of such devices in accordance with applicable law
  * Information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies (see additional descriptions of these terms below)
  * Information about your interactions with video content, such as the type of content viewed on our Services, and information about your interactions with email messages, such as the links you click on and whether you open or forward a message
  * Standard server log information

**Personalization and Tracking Technologies.** Like most website operators, we, or third parties acting on our behalf, use “cookies,” web beacons, and other similar technologies to recognize you and provide personalization, as well as to help us understand how our visitors use the website and how they spend their time there.

**Cookies.** Cookies are small amounts of data that are stored in separate files within your computer’s Internet browser. Cookies are accessed and recorded by the websites you visit, and by the companies that deliver the advertisements you see on websites, so they can recognize the same browser navigating online.

We use cookies for the following general purposes:

  * To help us recognize your browser as that of a previous visitor and save and remember any preferences that may have been set while your browser was visiting one of our websites. For example, if you register on a Midco website, we may save your username and/or password, so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit.
  * To help us customize the content and advertisements you see while using our Services and perhaps while visiting other websites online.
  * To help us measure, analyze, and improve the effectiveness of our interactive online content, features, advertisements, and other communications.

Third-party companies that provide some of the tools and features accessible through our Services and advertisers and other companies involved in the delivery of the advertisements that you see while using our Services also may place cookies within your browser. For example, in serving certain advertisements, some advertisers (or their agencies or vendors) may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser in order to collect certain non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our websites and to other sites. We do not have access to advertisers’ or service providers’ cookies and do not control how they may be used. You have the choice to set your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you before each cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) You can decide whether to allow us or third parties to send you cookies, but, if you block our cookies, you may not be able to view or access some of the features of our Services.

**Web Beacons and Other Tracking Technologies.** We, or third-party service providers acting on our behalf, may also use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and similar technologies, to track your use of our Services. Web beacons (sometimes called transparent GIFs, clear GIFs or pixel tags) are small strings of computer code that enable the delivery of a small graphic image (usually invisible) on a web page or in an email. When a web beacon is downloaded by your browser with the content of the page on which it appears, the server can recognize and store certain types of information, such as cookies that were previously set, the time and date the page embedded with the beacon was viewed, and a description of the page where the web beacon was placed. We use web beacons to improve your experience on our Services, such as providing you with content, advertising, and offers customized to your interests, and to understand whether users read email messages and click on links contained within those messages. Our Services may also include third-party web beacons that enable advertisers and other third-party companies to receive auditing, research, and reporting information about advertisements that you view while using our Services.

The use and collection of information by our third-party advertising service providers is governed by the individual privacy policies of those providers. For example, Synacor’s privacy policy can be found on the [Synacor website](http://www.synacor.com/legal/privacy.php "Synacor website"). Most of our advertising service providers, including Synacor, are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). You can obtain more information about these service providers’ information collection practices, and how you may opt out of such practices (and at the same time opt out of the collection practices of other, or all, NAI members) by following the opt-out instructions on the [NAI website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "NAI website").

Advertisers also may engage other third-party advertising service providers and analytics vendors to help them deliver advertisements tailored to your interests, and evaluate and improve the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns. We do not have access to the information these third parties may collect through cookies, web beacons or other technologies they use as you navigate within our Services and this Online Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of these third parties. You can opt out of the use of cookies by many of these third-party vendors to tailor advertising to you by visiting [Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program website](http://www.aboutads.info/ "About Ads website"). [  
](http://www.aboutads.info/)

**Mobile Device IDs and Location-Based Information.** Certain mobile devices, including smart phones and tablet devices, contain unique identifiers, sometimes known as “UDIDs,” that can be used to identify their physical location. Mobile devices also typically transmit caller ID data when used to transmit a telephone call or text message. When you rely on mobile devices to access our Services, we may collect and transmit UDIDs and collect caller ID data, the identity of the wireless provider associated with your telephone number, information on the location of your device, the make and model of your device, and similar information. We use this information to provide you the content and services you request, to tell you about offers we think you will value, and to improve your experience using our mobile applications and other Services. We also may collect your mobile phone number if you participate in certain services or features. Midco does not share UDIDs with third parties.

**Social Network Posting Tools and “Share” Features.** You can access various social network posting and sharing tools through our Services that are operated by third parties. For example, we offer a “share” button that allows you to post links on your social network pages to content and features you believe will be of interest to others. When you use one of these features to forward content to your friends or to post content to a social network page, the third-party service provider that operates the tool you are using may be collecting data through its own cookies or other processes we do not control. When you use any social networking or sharing tools available through our Services, any information you provide will be governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the tool you are using. These privacy policies may be different from ours. We encourage you to read them carefully.

**How We Use The Information We Collect:**

Our primary goal in collecting information is to provide you with a customized experience when using our Services and to make them more valuable to you. We only use payment and identity verification information, such as credit card numbers, driver’s license numbers, social security numbers, or comparable national identifiers as necessary for completing a particular transaction or fulfilling a service (such as paying for subscriptions or awarding prizes to contest winners), or as otherwise required by law.

We and our authorized service providers generally use other information collected about you to:

  * Operate and improve our Services, fulfill your requests for products, services, and information, including to send you electronic newsletters, authorize a purchase, and complete a transaction that you have requested;
  * Enable you to participate in features such as surveys, polls, sweepstakes, and message boards;
  * Provide you with special offers and promotional materials on behalf of Midco and third parties, in accordance with applicable law;
  * Analyze the use of our Services and information about our users to understand and improve our service offerings;
  * Customize the content you see when you use our Services;
  * Develop and provide advertising tailored to your interests, including advertising that you see for our Services and affiliated publications on third-party websites;
  * Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and enforce our Visitor Agreement;
  * Conduct market analysis, traffic flow analysis and related reporting; and
  * For any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or to which you consent.

**How We Disclose Information:**

Except as described below, we will not rent, sell or share personally identifying information that we collect about you without your prior consent:

**Name and Postal Address Lists.** If you provide us with your postal address, we may include that address in postal address lists that we maintain for internal purposes with Midco-affiliated companies and business divisions, but Midco does not sell or rent such postal address lists to third parties.

**Promotional Emails.** If you provide us with your email address and elect to receive promotional emails, from time to time we may send you emails about Midco publications, products, services, and special offers that we believe may be of interest to you. When you register, you will also be given an opportunity to tell us whether you would like to receive emails about products, services, and special offers from third-party providers. If do not wish to receive them, please go to My Account and update your preferences. Of course, you may change your preferences at any time. We will make any changes you request as quickly as we can. If you unsubscribe from a Midco email list, we reserve the right to disclose your opt-out information to third parties so they can suppress your address from future solicitations, in accordance with applicable laws.

**Provider Partners.** To make your experience with our Services more useful and enjoyable, we may offer some features (such as event photo galleries) in conjunction with third-party providers (“Provider Partners”) that specialize in operating them. We share with each of these Provider Partners the information necessary to provide you with features offered in conjunction with that Provider Partner. Their use of this information will be subject to the terms of their respective privacy policies, which you can find on their websites.

**Other Authorized Service Providers.** We also contract with other companies to provide specialized services on our behalf, including credit-card and billing processing, shipping, marketing, email and text message distribution, data processing, ad serving, business and website analytics, and promotions management. We reserve the right to share with these companies any information we collect about you provided that they commit to using the information solely to perform the services we request.

**Shopping.** When you are ready to make a purchase through one of our Services, we or the relevant merchant will ask you to provide certain information, including your contact details (such as your name, address, telephone, and email), and your billing information (such as your credit card number and the date that your card expires). If provided to us, we will use the information to process your transaction and to contact you regarding your purchase as necessary. We will share this information with the relevant merchant to the extent necessary to facilitate your purchase (for purposes such as customer service, verification, fulfillment, and billing purposes). We may share non-financial information with such merchants in accordance with this Online Privacy Policy.

**Affiliated Companies and Business Divisions.** We may share any information we collect about you with Midco-affiliated companies, so we can provide you with information about publications, products, and services that we believe might interest you.

**Aggregated Information.** We may combine information that we collect about you with information that we collect about other users of our Services and share it in a form that does not identify you personally. We may use such aggregated information and disclose it to third parties as we see fit.

**Information You Post to Blogs, Discussion Forums and Other Community Posting or Social Networking Areas.** Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information or other information available for viewing by third parties online – for example on blogs, discussion forums, or other community postings or social networking areas of one of our Services – that information can be seen, collected and used by anyone who has access to the service to which you posted. We cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third-party use of such information.

**Legal Compliance, Business Transfers, and Other Disclosures.** We may occasionally release information about users of our Services when release is appropriate to comply with law, respond to compulsory process or law enforcement requests, enforce our Visitor Agreement, or protect the rights, property, or safety of users of our Services, the public, Midco, our affiliates, or any third party. As our business evolves, we may reorganize or sell various assets. We reserve the right to transfer any information we collect in connection with a substantial corporate transaction or reorganization, such as the sale of a website or business division, a merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

**Sites to Which We Link.** We also may provide links to other websites, and provide access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase products or services or conduct other transactions through our Services, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services. When you provide information in the course of obtaining products or services through our Services, use of any information you provide may be governed by the privacy policy of the provider of those products or services, even if it appears that you are using one of our Services throughout the transaction. The provider’s privacy policy may differ from ours. If you cannot find the privacy policy of any of our providers through a link either from the site’s homepage or from the pages on which the products or services are offered, you should contact the provider directly for more information.

**How to Correct or Update Your Information:**

Midco believes in providing you with the ability to access and edit the personally identifying information that you have provided to us through our Services. To update this information, please visit [Midco.com/MyAccount](https://www.midco.com/myaccount "Midco My Account") or call 1.800.888.1300.

**Security:**

The personally identifying information we collect is stored in a database that we control. We use a variety of procedures and technologies to protect your information. As effective as these technologies may be, however, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.

**Retention and Storage of Information:**

For the purposes set out in this Online Privacy Policy, personally-identifying information may be transferred to, processed, stored, and accessed by us or one of our affiliates or an unaffiliated service provider in the United States or other jurisdictions where we or they may have operations. Courts and other authorities in these jurisdictions may, in certain circumstances, be entitled to access your personally-identifying information. By using the Services, you consent to this transfer, processing, storage, and access of your personally-identifying information in and/or outside of the jurisdiction in which you reside.

**Changes to Our Online Privacy Policy:**

The Internet is an evolving medium. If we need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, we will post the changes before they take effect.

**Questions:**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of this site, please contact us by sending a letter to:

Midco  
Attn: Chief Legal Officer  
3901 North Louise Avenue   
Sioux Falls, SD 57107

If you have any questions about our services, your dealings with this site, or to contact someone about the services offered by Midco, please contact us at 1.800.888.1300.
